case_id gold_intent predicted_intent  should_escalate selected_evidence_response_type  selected_evidence_similarity                                                                                                                                                                                                                                            reply
 VZ-001         I06              I06            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                                         Can you uninstall and reinstall the App?
 VZ-002         I01              I01            False                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-003         I02              I02            False                   clarification                      1.000000 We were asking because the next step in troubleshooting would be to factory reset the router. If any settings in the router have been changed they will default back to the information on the sticker. Can you please factory reset the router?
 VZ-004         I10              I10             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-005         I07              I08             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-006         I12              I07             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-007         I04              I04            False                 troubleshooting                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                         We are working on it. You can check at for updates regarding the matter.
 VZ-008         I12              I11             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-009         I11              I11             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-010         I02              I02            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                   Our apologies as we want you connected. Is this happening over a wired or wireless connection?
 VZ-011         I04              I04            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-012         I02              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-013         I11              I11             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-014         I05              I05            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-015         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-016         I04              I04            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                          Could you do me a favor and reboot the router and then that box please?
 VZ-017         I04              I04            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-018         I07              I10             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-019         I05              I05            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-020         I02              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-021         I08              I08             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-022         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-023         I10              I10             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-024         I06              I06            False                 troubleshooting                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                     Our apologies as we have gotten reports and the issue is being investigated.
 VZ-025         I04              I04            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-026         I04              I04            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                                                  Are all the channels clear now?
 VZ-027         I05              I09            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                 Is this for your Verizon residential or Verizon wireless mobile?
 VZ-028         I04              I04            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                                   That's odd. Do you mean the picture is tiling?
 VZ-029         I08              I08             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-030         I04              I08             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-031         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-032         I02              I02             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-033         I04              I04            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                   Are you attempting to view it on your TV using the cable card?
 VZ-034         I08              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-035         I10              I10             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-036         I04              I07             True                 troubleshooting                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-037         I09              I09            False                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-038         I09              I09             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-039         I11              I11             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-040         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-041         I12              I02             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-042         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-043         I03              I03            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                      What questions do you have? We can answer your questions be we do not recommend equipment .
 VZ-044         I02              I02             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-045         I08              I08             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-046         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-047         I04              I02             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-048         I02              I02             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-049         I10              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-050         I05              I05             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-051         I12              I07             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-052         I11              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-053         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-054         I08              I08             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-055         I07              I07             True                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-056         I11              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-057         I09              I09            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                           Do you have digital voice or copper for phone service?
 VZ-058         I06              I06            False                   clarification                      0.318034                                                                                                                                                          Oh no, is this happening to all sites? Do you happen to have Tracerts for us to review?
 VZ-059         I11              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-060         I06              I06            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-061         I11              I11             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-062         I06              I05            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-063         I02              I02            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                   We want to provide the correct support. Is this regarding your Mobile or Residential services?
 VZ-064         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-065         I02              I02            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-066         I07              I07             True                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-067         I03              I03            False                 troubleshooting                      1.000000                                                                                                                       Great, if you have the white unit hold down the alarm silence button for 20 secs. The black unit will have a reset button.
 VZ-068         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-069         I02              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-070         I09              I09             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-071         I01              I03            False                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-072         I03              I08             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-073         I11              I11             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-074         I03              I02             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-075         I07              I07             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-076         I07              I07             True                  account_action                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-077         I02              I02             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-078         I09              I09             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-079         I02              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-080         I11              I07             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-081         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-082         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-083         I03              I03            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                           Are you able to run a speed test using the link below?
 VZ-084         I06              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-085         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-086         I11              I11             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-087         I11              I03            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-088         I03              I03            False                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-089         I12              I04            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-090         I08              I08             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-091         I02              I02             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-092         I09              I09            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                       Are you referring to your wireless device or home service?
 VZ-093         I06              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-094         I02              I02            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                                  Can you try to run it from a different browser?
 VZ-095         I01              I01            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                 Good evening, was this an issue with your home or cell internet?
 VZ-096         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-097         I11              I11             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-098         I01              I01            False                 troubleshooting                      0.364341                                                                                                           We understand how important it is to have an internet connection. Our techs will work to get it up and running as soon as is possible.
 VZ-099         I02              I02             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-100         I08              I08             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-101         I01              I01            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                               Oh no! Are you going to make the appointment time?
 VZ-102         I02              I02            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                                                     What speeds are you getting?
 VZ-103         I09              I09            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                 Is this for your Verizon residential or Verizon wireless mobile?
 VZ-104         I09              I09             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-105         I02              I07             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-106         I09              I09             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-107         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-108         I06              I04             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-109         I12              I07             True                 troubleshooting                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-110         I09              I09            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-111         I11              I11             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-112         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-113         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-114         I10              I10             True                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-115         I04              I04            False                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-116         I08              I08             True                 troubleshooting                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-117         I01              I01            False                   clarification                      0.344575                                                                                                                                                                                     Oh no, Do you know where the Battery Backup unit is located?
 VZ-118         I02              I03            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                                   Can you perform a factory reset on the router?
 VZ-119         I12              I04            False                 troubleshooting                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                                                             Check out this link.
 VZ-120         I12              I02             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-121         I03              I03            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                         Perfect! Can you hold down the Alarm Silence button for 15 seconds? Wait 5 minutes afterwards to see if services return.
 VZ-122         I07              I07             True                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-123         I10              I10             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-124         I10              I10             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-125         I02              I02            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-126         I02              I02            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                      No worries if you don't have any Ethernet connected devices. Can you install the My Fios app on any of your mobile devices?
 VZ-127         I02              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-128         I10              I10             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-129         I12              I04            False                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-130         I03              I03             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-131         I11              I11             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-132         I01              I01            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                              Is the internet light currently lit on your router? If so, what color is it? Also, do you have Fios or DSL with us?
 VZ-133         I11              I11             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-134         I10              I10             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-135         I03              I03            False                 troubleshooting                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                              There should be an ONT reset button. Hold that down for 15 seconds.
 VZ-136         I10              I10             True                  account_action                      0.315002                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-137         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-138         I07              I07             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-139         I08              I03            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-140         I04              I08             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-141         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-142         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-143         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-144         I03              I03            False                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-145         I12              I04            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-146         I02              I02            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                                         Have you reset the battery back up unit?
 VZ-147         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-148         I07              I07             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-149         I06              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-150         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-151         I11              I03            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                 Is this for your Verizon residential or Verizon wireless mobile?
 VZ-152         I11              I11             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-153         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-154         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-155         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-156         I04              I07             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-157         I11              I11             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-158         I08              I08             True                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-159         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-160         I05              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-161         I02              I03            False                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-162         I08              I08             True                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-163         I11              I11             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-164         I07              I07             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-165         I04              I04            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                                          That's odd! Does this occur often Zack?
 VZ-166         I04              I04            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                       Oh no, what is making you feel this way? Let us know, we are here to help.
 VZ-167         I07              I07             True                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-168         I01              I03            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                       Uh Oh! Is the internet light currently lit on your router?
 VZ-169         I01              I03             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-170         I06              I04             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-171         I03              I03            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                 Are any devices connected other than the one you are testing on?
 VZ-172         I02              I03            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                  You can reset the system. Do you know where the Battery Backup unit is located?
 VZ-173         I02              I02            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                              Oh no, is that over a wired or wireless connection?
 VZ-174         I01              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-175         I11              I11             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-176         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-177         I08              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-178         I03              I03            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                         Understood, it sounds like it may be over utilization. How many devices are connected wired and wirelessly to the modem?
 VZ-179         I10              I10             True                  account_action                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-180         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-181         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-182         I12              I01            False                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                Thanks for reaching out. We found a related historical case, but it does not provide enough actionable information to safely recommend a fix. A support agent should review this.
 VZ-183         I12              I10             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-184         I08              I03            False                   clarification                      0.535387                                                                                                                                                                                                      What did the agent on the phone advise you?
 VZ-185         I10              I10             True                      escalation                      1.000000                                                                                                       Thanks for flagging this. Because this involves potential unauthorized activity, a human support agent should review the account securely.
 VZ-186         I12              I07             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-187         I04              I04             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-188         I12              I07             True                 troubleshooting                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-189         I06              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-190         I09              I09             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-191         I08              I08             True                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                      Thanks for reaching out. Installation and technician scheduling require account-specific assistance, so a support agent should review the details with you.
 VZ-192         I03              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-193         I02              I02            False                 troubleshooting                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                                   Hi Mike, Use this link to check out Fios TV plans and channels
 VZ-194         I12              I11             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                     We're sorry for the frustration. This needs to be reviewed by a human support agent so they can look into the issue and assist you directly.
 VZ-195         I04              I04            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                            We can help right here. What seems to be going on with your services?
 VZ-196         I05              I07             True                         unknown                      1.000000                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. Billing and payment issues may require account-specific verification, so a support agent should review the account details with you.
 VZ-197         I01              I01             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                                 Thanks for reaching out. A support agent should review the details and help determine the appropriate next step.
 VZ-198         I06              I06            False                   clarification                      1.000000                                                                                                                                                                             We're here for you! Is this for a Fios or Wireless (mobile) account?
 VZ-199         I12              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
 VZ-200         I07              I12             True                             NaN                           NaN                                                                                                                    Thanks for reaching out. We need a little more information to understand the issue before we can provide the right next step.
